<xmltest>
<table>     

<td languagename="Arabic" languageid="ar">
أوروبا, برمجيات الحاسوب
+ انترنيت :
    تصبح عالميا مع يونيكود
تسجّل الآن
لحضور المؤتمر الدولي العاشر ليونيكود, الذي
سيعقد في 10-12 آذار 1997 بمدينة ماينتس, ألمانيا.
وسيجمع المؤتمر بين خبراء من  كافة قطاعات الصناعة
على الشبكة العالمية انترنيت ويونيكود, حيث
ستتم, على الصعيدين الدولي والمحلي على حد سواء
مناقشة سبل استخدام يونكود  في النظم القائمة
وفيما يخص التطبيقات الحاسوبية, الخطوط, تصميم
النصوص  والحوسبة متعددة اللغات.
عندما يريد
العالم أن يتكلّم, فهو يتحدّث بلغة يونيكود.
</td>

<td languagename="Catalan" languageid="ca">
Europa, software + Internet:
    mundialitzant amb Unicode
Inscrigui's ara a la Desena Conferència Internacional Unicode, que 
tindrá lloc del 10 al 12 de març de 1997 a Magúncia (Alemanya). La 
Conferència reunirà experts dels sectors de la mundialització d'Internet 
i Unicode, la internacionalització i localització, implementació de  
Unicode en sistemes operatius i aplicacions, tipus, composició de text i 
informàtica multilingüe.
Quan el món vol conversar, parla Unicode
</td>

<td languagename="Chinese (Simplified)" languageid="zh-cn">
欧洲，软件＋互联网
    用统一码 (Unicode) 走遍世界
将于1997年 3 月10日－12日在德国  Mainz
市举行的第十届统一码国际研讨会现在开始注册。
本次会议将汇集各方面的专家。
涉及的领域包括：
国际互联网和统一码
，国际化和本地化
，统一码在操作系统和应用软件中的实现
，字型
，文本格式以及多文种计算等。
当世界需要沟通时，请用Unicode！
</td>



<td languagename="Chinese (Traditional)" languageid="zh-tw">
歐洲，軟體及網際網路：
    讓統一碼（Unicode）領你進入全世界
你現在就應報名將在１９９７年３月１０至１２日於德國美姿城（Mainz）
召開的第十屆國際統一碼研討會。
本次研討會將邀請多位業界專家研討
關於全球網際網路及統一碼發展、
國際化及本土化、
支援統一碼的作業系統及應用
程式、
字型、
文字排版、
電腦多國語文化等多項課題。
當世界需要溝通時，請用統一碼（Unicode）
</td>



<td languagename="Danish" languageid="da">
Europa, Software + Internet:
    Bliv global med Unicode
Indskriv dig nu til den tiende internationale
Unicode-konference, der holdes den 10-12 marts 1997 i Mainz, Tyskland. Konferencen
samler eksperter fra hele verden inden for det globale Internet og Unicode,
internationalisering og lokalisering, implementering af Unicode i styresystemer
og programmer, skrifttyper, tekst-layout og flersproget databehandling.
Når verden vil tale, taler den Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Dutch" languageid="nl">
Europa, Software + het Internet:
    wereldwijd met Unicode
Meld u nu aan voor de Tiende Internationale Unicode-conferentie, die
van 10 tot 12 maart 1997 in Mainz (Duitsland) wordt gehouden. De
Conferentie is een ontmoetingsplaats voor experts uit de industrie op
het gebied van het wereldwijde Internet en Unicode,
internationalisatie en localisatie, implementatie van Unicode in
besturingssystemen en applicaties, lettertypes, tekstopmaak en
meertalig computergebruik.
Als de wereld wil praten, spreekt hij Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="English" languageid="en">
Europe, Software + the Internet:
    Going Global with Unicode
         Register now for the Tenth International Unicode Conference, to be held on 
         March 10-12, 1997, in Mainz, Germany.  The Conference will bring together 
         industry-wide experts on the global Internet and Unicode, internationalization 
         and localization, implementation of Unicode in operating systems and applications, 
         fonts, text layout, and multilingual computing.
When the world wants to talk, it speaks Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Esperanto" languageid="eo">
Eŭropo, programaroj kaj Interreto:
    tutmondiĝu per Unicode
Aliĝu al la 10a Internacia Unicode-konferenco, en Mainz, Germanio.
Ĝi daŭros de la 10a ĝis la 12a de marto 1997.  La konferenco kunigos 
fakulojn kaj spertulojn pri la jenaj temoj: Interreto kaj Unicode, 
adaptado al internaciaj kaj lokaj kondiĉoj, realigo de Unicode en 
mastrumaj sistemoj kaj aplikprogramoj, litertiparoj, enpaĝigado de teksto,
kaj plurlingva komputilumado.
Kiam la mondo volas paroli, ĝi parolas Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Finnish" languageid="fi">
Eurooppa, ohjelmisto ja internet:
    Unicode vie maailmalle
Rekisteröidy nyt kymmenenteen kansainväliseen Unicode -konferenssiin,
joka pidetään 10.-12. maaliskuuta 1997 Mainzissa Saksassa. Konferenssi
kokoaa yhteen internetin ja Unicoden, kansainvälistämisen ja
lokalisoinnin, Unicode-toteutusten, kirjasimien, tekstin muotoilun ja
monikielisen tiedonkäsittelyn asiantuntijat.
Kun maailma haluaa puhua, se puhuu Unicodea
</td>



<td languagename="French" languageid="fr">
L'Europe, le logiciel et l'Internet :
    la mondialisation avec Unicode
   Inscrivez-vous dès maintenant à la dixième Conférence internationale sur
Unicode, qui se tiendra du 10 au 12 mars 1997 à Mayence, en Allemagne. Cette
conférence rassemblera des experts de tous les horizons industriels sur les
sujets suivants : l'Internet mondial et Unicode, l'internationalisation et
l'adaptation locale, l'implémentation d'Unicode dans les systèmes
d'exploitation et les applications, les polices de caractères, la disposition
de texte, l'informatique plurilingue.
Quand le monde veut communiquer, il parle en Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Georgian" languageid="ka">
ევროპა, პროგრამული უზრუნველყოფა + ინტერნეტი:
    Unicode-ი მთელს მსოფლიოში
      გთხოვთ ახლავე გაიაროთ რეგისტრაცია Unicode-ის მეათე საერთაშორისო
      კონფერენციაზე დასასწრებად, რომელიც გაიმართება 10-12 მარტს, 
      ქ. მაინცში, გერმანიაში. კონფერენცია შეჰკრებს ერთად მსოფლიოს
      ექსპერტებს ისეთ დარგებში როგორიცაა ინტერნეტი და Unicode-ი, 
      ინტერნაციონალიზაცია და ლოკალიზაცია,  Unicode-ის გამოყენება        
      ოპერაციულ სისტემებსა,  და  გამოყენებით პროგრამებში, შრიფტებში, 
      ტექსტების დამუშავებასა და მრავალენოვან კომპიუტერულ სისტემებში.
როდესაც მსოფლიოს ურთირთობა სურს, იგი Unicode-ის ენაზე ლაპარაკობს
</td>



<td languagename="German" languageid="de">
Europa, Software + das Internet:
    International mit Unicode
Melden Sie sich jetzt für die 10. Internationale Unicode Konferenz
an, die in der Zeit vom 10.-12. März 1997 in Mainz stattfinden wird.
Die Konferenz ist ein Treffpunkt für Betriebsexperten aus den Bereichen
globales Internet und Unicode, Internationalisierung und Lokalisierung,
die Implementierung von Unicode in Betriebssystemen und Programmen, sowie
für Schriftarten, Textlayout und mehrsprachige Computeranwendungen.
Wenn die Welt miteinander spricht, spricht sie Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Hebrew" languageid="he">
אירופה, תוכנה והאינטרנט:
    Unicode יוצא לשוק העולמי
הירשמו
כעת לכנס Unicode הבינלאומי העשירי,
שייערך בין התאריכים 12־10 במרץ 1997, במיינץ שבגרמניה.
בכנס ישתתפו מומחים מכל ענפי התעשייה בנושא
האינטרנט העולמי וה־Unicode,
בהתאמה לשוק הבינלאומי והמקומי, ביישום 
Unicode במערכות הפעלה וביישומים,
בגופנים, בפריסת טקסט ובמחשוב רב־לשוני.
כאשר העולם
רוצה לדבר, הוא מדבר ב־Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Hungarian" languageid="hu">
Európa, a Szoftver s az Internet -
    Globálissá Változik a Unicode Által
Iratkozzon már most a Tizedik
Nemzetközi Unicode Konferenciára, amely Március 10-12 1997 lesz  megtartva,
Meinz-be, Németországba. Ebben a Konferencián az iparág szerte sok szakértő
fog részt venni: a globális Internet s Unicode nemzetközisítése s lokalizálása,
a Unicode beteljesítése a működő rendszerekben s alkalmazásokban, fontokba,
szöveg térbeosztásba s többnyelvű computerekben.
Ha a világ beszélni akar, azt Unicode-ul mondja
</td>



<td languagename="Irish Gaelic" languageid="ga">
An Eoraip, Earra Bog + an tIdirghréasán:
    Gréasánú Domhanda le hUnicode
Cláraigh anois don Deichiú Comhdháil Idirnáisiúnta de chuid Unicode, a
bheidh ar siúl 10-12 Márta 1997, i Mainz na Gearmáine. Tabharfaidh an
Chomhdháil seo daoine le chéile atá eolach ar gach gné den tionscal --
ar an Idirghréasán domhanda, ar Unicode, ar aistriú agus ar chóiriú
áitiúil earra bhoig, ar fheidhmiú Unicode i gcórais oibre agus i
bhfeidhmchláir, ar chlófhoirne, ar leagan amach téacs, agus ar
ríomhaireacht ilteangach i gcoitinne.
Nuair a bhualann fonn cainte an domhan, is as Unicode a labhrann sé
</td>



<td languagename="Italian" languageid="it">
Europa, software e Internet:
    Globalizzazione con Unicode
Iscrivetevi subito alla X Conferenza Internazionale
su Unicode, che si terrà dal
10 al 12 marzo 1997 a Mainz in Germania. Alla Conferenza parteciperanno esperti
di tutti i settori per discutere di Internet globale e Unicode, internazionalizzazione
e localizzazione, implementazione di Unicode in sistemi operativi e applicazioni,
caratteri, composizione dei testi ed elaborazione multilingue.
Quando il mondo vuole comunicare, parla Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Japanese" languageid="ja">
ヨーロッパ、ソフトウェア、そしてインターネット:
    Unicode でグローバル化を狙って
第 10 回の Unicode 会議は 1997 年 3 月 10～12日、ドイツのマインツで開
かれます。参加希望の方は今すぐ登録してください。
この会議では、グローバ
ルなインタネット、Unicode、ソフトウェアの国際化およびローカリゼーショ
ン、OS およびアプリケーションでの Unicode のインプリメンテーション、フォ
ント、テキスト表示、マルチ言語コンピューティングにおける業界の専門家が
集まります。
世界的に話すなら、Unicode です。
</td>



<td languagename="Korean" languageid="ko">
유럽, 소프트웨어 그리고 인터넷:
    유니코드와 함께 세계로
제10회 유니코드 국제 회의가 1997년 3월 10일부터 12일까지 독일의 마인즈에서 열립니다.
지금 등록하십시오.
이 회의에서는 업계 전반의 전문가들이 함께 모여 다음과 같은 분야를 다룹니다.
- 인터넷과 유니코드, 국제화와 지역화, 운영 체제와 응용 프로그램에서 유니코드의 구현,
글꼴, 문자 배열, 다국어 컴퓨팅.
세계를 향한 대화, 유니코드로 하십시오
</td>



<td languagename="Norwegian (Bokmål)" languageid="no-bok">
Europa, Programvare og Internet:
    Global fokus med Unicode
Registrer deg som deltager på den tiende inernasjonale Unicode konferansen i 
Mainz, Tyskland, fra 10. til 12. mars, 1997. Konferansen vil samle eksperter på 
Internet, Unicode, internasjonalisering og integrasjon av Unicode i 
operativsystemer og programmer, fonter, tekst layout og flerspråklig 
databehandling.
Når verden vil snakke, snakker den Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Norwegian (Nynorsk)" languageid="no-nyn">
Europa, programvare og Internett:
    Femn verda med Unicode
Meld deg på den 10. internasjonale Unicode-konferansen.
Han går føre seg i Mainz i
Tyskland i dagane 10.--12. mars 1997, og samlar fagkunnige innan
konferansetemaet frå heile databransjen. Tema: Det globale
Internettet og Unicode, internasjonalisering og nasjonal tilpassing,
implementering av Unicode i operativsystem og brukarprogram,
skriftsnitt (fontar), tekstutlegg, og fleirspråkleg databehandling.
Når verda ønskjer å snakke, talar ho Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Occitan" languageid="oc">
Europa, logicial + Internet:
    mondializant ambe Unicode
Inscrivetz-vos ara a la dezena Conferència internacionala
sobre Unicode, que se tendrà del 10 al 12 de març
de 1997 a Maiença (Alemanha). La Conferència reunirà 
d'experts dels sectors de la mondializacion d'Internet e d'Unicode, de
l'internacionalizacion e localizacion, de l'implementacion de l'Unicode
en de sistemas operatius, en aplicacions, caractèrs tipografics,
tractament de text e informatica multilinga.
Quan lo mond vòl conversar, parla en Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Portuguese (Brazil)" languageid="pt-br">
Europa, Software e a Internet:
    Globalização com o Unicode
Inscreva-se agora para a Décima Conferência Internacional Sobre O Unicode, realizada entre os dias 10 e 12 de março de 1997 em Mainz 
na Alemanha. A Conferência reunirá peritos de todas as áreas da indústria especializados em assuntos relacionados com a Internet 
global e o Unicode, internacionalização e localização de software, implementação do Unicode em sistemas operacionais e aplicativos, 
fontes, layout de texto e informática multilíngüe.
Quando o mundo quer falar, fala Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Portuguese (Portugal)" languageid="pt-pt">
Europa, Software e a Internet:
    Globalização com o Unicode
Inscreva-se agora para a Décima Conferência Internacional Sobre O Unicode, a ser realizada entre os dias 10 e 12 de Março de 1997 em 
Mainz na Alemanha. A Conferência reunirá peritos de todas as áreas da indústria especializados em assuntos relacionados com a 
Internet global e o Unicode, internacionalização e localização de software, implementação do Unicode em sistemas operativos e 
aplicações, tipos de letra, esquematização de texto e informática multilíngue.
Quando o mundo quer falar, fala Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Romanian" languageid="rp">
Europa, Software şi Internet:
    Globalizarea cu Unicode
Inscrieţi-vă acum la a Zecea Conferinţă Internaţională "Unicode" ce va avea loc  
in perioada de 10-12 martie, 1997 în Mainz, Germania. Conferinţa va întruni 
experţi din variate domenii: Internet global şi Unicode, internaţionalizare şi 
localizare, implementare de Unicode în sisteme de operare şi aplicaţii, fonturi, 
aranjare de text în pagină, computerizare multilinguală. 
Când lumea vrea să comunice, vorbeşte Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Russian" languageid="ru">
Европа, Программное обеспечение
+ Интернет:
    Unicode в глобальных масштабах
Зарегистрируйтесь сейчас
на Десятую Международную Конференцию по
Unicode, которая состоится 10-12 марта 1997 года в
Майнце в Германии. Конференция соберет широкий
круг экспертов по  вопросам глобального Интернета
и Unicode, локализации и интернационализации,
воплощению и применению Unicode в различных
операционных системах и программных приложениях,
шрифтах, верстке и многоязычных компьютерных
системах.
Когда мир желает общаться,
он общается на Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Slovenian" languageid="sl">
Evropa, programje in Internet:
    globalizacija z Unicodom
Prijavite se na Deseto mednarodno konferenco Unicode, ki bo med 10. in 12.
marcem v Mainzu, Nemčija.  Konferenca bo zbrala svetovno znane izvedence
za globalni Internet in Unicode, internacionalizacijo in lokalizacijo,
izvedbe Unicode v različnih operacijskih sistemih in programe, fonte,
stavljenje besedila in večjezično računalništvo.
Ko se želi svet pogovarjati, govori Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Spanish" languageid="es">
Europa, Software + el Internet:
    Mundializando con Unicode
Inscríbase ahora para la Décima Conferencia Internacional Unicode, que
tendrá lugar del 10 al 12 de marzo de 1997 en Maguncia, Alemania.  La
Conferencia reunirá expertos de los sectores de la mundialización del
Internet y Unicode, la internacionalización y localización,
implementación de Unicode en sistemas operativos y aplicaciones, tipos,
composición de texto e informática multilingüe.
Cuando el mundo quiere conversar, habla Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Swedish" languageid="sv">
Europa, programvara och Internet:
    globalisera med Unicode
Anmäl Dig till den tionde internationella Unicode-konferensen, som
hålls den 10-12 mars 1997 i Mainz, Tyskland.  Vid konferensen kommer
experter inom följande områden att delta: det globala Internet och
Unicode, internationalisering och lokalisering, implementering av
Unicode i operativsystem, tillämpningar, typsnitt, textlayout och
mångspråklig datoranvändning.
När världen vill tala, så talar den Unicode
</td>



<td languagename="Yiddish" languageid="yi">
אײראָפּע: פּראָגראַמװאַרג און די װעלטנעץ:
    אוניקאָד איבער דער גאָרער װעלט 
פֿאַרשרײַבט זיך שױן אױף דער צענטער אינטערנאַציאָנאַלער אוניקאָד-קאָנפֿערענץ, װאָס װעט 
פֿאָרקומען דעם 10טן ביזן 12טן מאַרץ, 1997, אין מײַנץ, דײַטשלאַנד.  די קאָנפֿערענץ 
װעט צוזאַמענברענגן מבֿינים פֿון װעלטנעץ, אוניקאָד, אי אַלװעלטלעכן אי סבֿיבֿהדיקן 
פּראָגראַמװאַרג, אַרײַנשטעלן אוניקאָד אין אָפּעריר-סיסטעמען און אָנװענדונגען, שריפֿטן, 
טעקסט-אױסשטעל, און מערשפּראַכיקע קאָמפּיוטערײַ. 
אַז די װעלט װיל רעדן, רעדט זי אוניקאָד
</td>




</table>

</xmltest>